(Sheldon(shouting):)We've gotten a little off-topic.
(Sheldon(shouting):)Allow me to make things
entertaining again
(Sheldon(shouting):)in this little Spockumentary.
(Sheldon(shouting):)That was Leonard's joke.
(Sheldon(shouting):)As a child,
when faced with a dilemma,
(Sheldon(shouting):)my mother encouraged me to ask,
“What would Jesus do?”
(Sheldon(shouting):)The answer to that was always,
“Love thy neighbor.”
But my neighbor had
a dead tooth, so...
(Sheldon(shouting):)that wasn't going to happen.
(Howard:)But...
(Sheldon(shouting):)that's why I changed it
to, “What would Spock do?”
(Adam:)Did you find that helpful?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Oh, for example,
three years ago
(Sheldon:)when I discovered Penny
was eating all my Pop-Tarts,
(Sheldon:)instead of getting angry
or vindictive,
(Sheldon:)you know, I got a floor safe.